createcoolapps.com 2012-11-05

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

DIME Consultants Inc. has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: http://www.CreateCoolApps.com.

Simply put, we NEVER rent, sell or give out your private information unless required by law. For more legal details, read on:

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to help identify you and your shopping cart and to gather broad demographic information, as well as to protect against fraud. We track IP addresses on all order forms for this reason.

Our site uses cookies to keep track of your user log in. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, possibly to save your password so you don’t have to re-enter it each time you visit our site, and for other purposes such as for affiliate tracking and site membership.

Our site’s registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address) and in some instances, unique identifiers (like their social security number). We may use customer contact information from the registration form to send the user information about our company and promotional material in the form of newsletter or website ads. We do not share our client’s private information with our partners or any advertisers.

The customer’s contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings. Opt Out information is on every mailing we send. Unique identifiers (such as social security numbers) are collected to verify the user’s identity and for use as account numbers in our affiliate record system.

Log Files  
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

Cookies and Web Beacons  
We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

We do not personally use web beacons for any tracking purposes in our system or in our apps.

However, app creators may use such information tools, so please be sure to read the policies of each app.

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as F-Secure Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

**APP TESTING**

**Our mobile apps (particularly our Previewer apps), may request your location, access to your camera, recorder, or other similar device settings. This is solely used in our Previewer apps for the purpose of testing other apps, to ensure they work.**

**We never track, monitor, or attempt to report to anyone your private details.**

**If in the event our regular apps request the same information, (i.e., access to your camera, to give you a certain function of the app, or your location in order to provide you with local information), the same policy applies: we never rent, share, sell, trade or report to anyone your personal information.**

**We believe in the utmost safety of our users and will always abide by these guidelines. Your privacy is safe with us.**

**Only usage data may be saved by us (i.e., the number of users in an area, or the number of users who accessed a feature, just like how a website knows how many visitors it has had) but we will never release or track personal data.  
**

This site contains links to other sites. DIME Consultants Inc. is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites outside of the DIME Consultants ownership. (See Terms of Use.)

Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect visitor’s contact information (like their email address) and financial information (like their account or credit card numbers). Contact information from the order form is used to process orders and verify for fraud protection. The customer’s contact information is used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary, but is not sold, rented or traded.

Paid Users may opt-out of receiving future newsletter mailings. Removal links are included in every email, and in the members area. Members are required to receive occasional system updates that pertain to all members while active. If any member does not wish to receive system updates, they must cancel their membership.

Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services. Our online surveys may ask visitors for contact information (like their email address) and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level).

We use contact data from our surveys to send the user information about our company and occasional promotional material from some of our partners. The customer’s contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. However, we never release this information to any public entity.

Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor our visitor’s experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences.

SECURITY  
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.

CHOICE/OPT-OUT  
Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at the point where we request information about the visitor.

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service if the member is free.

Opt Out instructions are included in any mailings. To opt out from the website, Go to our contact page and notify support at the applicable site. You must enter the email address listed with us for us to be able to remove you.

CONTACTING THE WEBSITE  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can visit our Contact Page for direct contact information.
